Peach Boy Dumplings
Brought to you by: Ko-Fi.me/OrangeFlash
Damn you, Nobita! I'll beat you up once I find you!
Same here!
Where did he go? Dammit!
I'll pulverize you.
Where'd he go?
Doraemon!
Giant and Suneo are after me.
What am I supposed to do now?
Again?
Please help me!
You're so hopeless!
Peach Boy Dumplings!
How do I use it?
Make Giant eat this!
Nobita! You have left the door open and put your shoes untidy.
You need to assort everything.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Seriously! Try being obedient to your mum!
Didn't you promise to do your homework when you're home?
Sit!
Turn around!
Now go!
Mum?
Is it OK to leave her like that? For how long does it's effects last?
No worries. She'll be back to normal in no time.
These are the dumplings which are used to...
tame wild beasts in the 22nd century.
When an animal is fed these dumplings...
they start obeying commands of their tamers.
Zoos and circuses of the 22nd century use...
...this gadget to tame and control the wild animals.
Enough of your lecture! Please lend it to me already!
Sure, but you must not play pranks on anybody.
Thanks! Now I can be in peace.
Let's see where Giant is!
I didn't find him!
Found 'em!
Have one of these dumplings each.
Stop!
Hey stop!
Oh,my! Welcome, Nobita-kun.
Shizuka-chan!
He's inside her home.
He's coming out!
What's wrong?
Nothing really.
Why don't we play a game, Shizuka-chan?
it's now your turn, Shizuka-chan.
Yup.
Damn it! They are still there!
What are you saying?
Oh, my!
Is this for me?
RIght!
Thanks!
Yum!
Damn you, Nobita!
How terrifying! Wish I had a horse!
What horse?
She must have ate one of these!
Give these to Giant and Suneo!
He's here! Huh?
Shizuka-chan?
You're giving us dumplings? Thanks!
There they eat it! Yes!
Bye!
Stop, Nobita!
Crawl!
This is so much fun!
Why are we crawling on the road like this?
Stop! Damn you!
Sit down!
Stop!
Circle around.
Why don't you fight with each other?
Nobita-kun, did it work well?
As you can see...
Isn't it fun to see them like this?
Peach Boy Dumpling is working as I expected it to.